Guide to the Mirra Ginsburg Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series XI: Oversized
  - Winn, Marie "What Become of Childhood Innocence", New York Times Magazine, Jan. 25, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis; Congrat-Butlar, Stephan Singer photos, New York, NY, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 6)